<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dude Ways</string>

    <string name="splash1">"Welcome to our travel community, where every journey begins with a new friendship"</string>
    <string name="splash2">"Where wanderlust meets companionship - find your perfect travel partner today!"</string>
    <string name="splash3">"Join a global network of explorers and find your ideal travel buddy."</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">By continuing you agree to our \n<u>Terms of Service Privacy Policy \nContent Policy</u></string>
    <string name="id_verification_description">An ID verification helps us check that you are a real person and you are really you. It also helps us keep secure and trustworthy. How does it work?\n\nFirst you will add a picture of yourself and provide a clear picture of your ID. We will then quickly match both the pictures.</string>
    <string name="more"><u>more...</u></string>
    <string name="less"><u>less...</u></string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">789941112934-hh4j9ueivjq4uei4e2k3g3414qvmhnod.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="look_straight_to_the_camera">Look straight to the Camera</string>

    <string-array name="days_of_week">
        <item>Sunday</item>
        <item>Monday</item>
        <item>Tuesday</item>
        <item>Wednesday</item>
        <item>Thursday</item>
        <item>Friday</item>
        <item>Saturday</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-8693482193769963~4468032819</string>
    <string name="privacyandpolicy">Your privacy is important to us, and we use your Personal Information only for providing and improving our services. By using our services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. These Terms apply to all visitors, users, and others who access or use the service.\nInformation Collection And Use\n\n\nWhile using our services, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name and email address (\"Personal Information\"). We will also collect non-identifiable information that does not allow direct association with any specific individual, as well as your profile info, travel updates, and any other account-associated details for our marketing and analytical purposes.\n\n\nThis includes cookies and other technologies to improve our users’ experience and the overall performance of our services. We can share information with our third-party partners in different cases as well.\n\n\nWe use the information collected:\n\n\n    To communicate with you;\n    To improve our services and see the number of users;\n    To customize the services, advertisements, and/or products we provide to you;\n    To assist with our product and service development;\n    To perform marketing analysis; and\n    For other purposes related to our business.\n\n\nWhen you create a Dudeways account, you will be asked to sign in using your email address or Facebook, LinkedIn, Google, or any other email account. This will authorize us to access your public information from those accounts, consistent with your privacy settings. You will have an option to invite your Facebook/LinkedIn friends to join Dudeways, which will allow us to access your friend list on those websites.\n\n\nFor us to provide you with travel reservation services, and as may be required by our compliance policy, except for instances where we indicate that particular information can be submitted voluntarily, you will need to provide Personal Information in order to make a reservation. Not doing so can prevent us from completing the transaction and providing you with requested information. You can always control the use of your Personal Information for direct marketing by unsubscribing from emails.\n\n\nIf you are purchasing travel services as a third party for others, you will need to have the right to provide the passengers’ personal information to us and confirm that they accept how Dudeways uses their information as stated in this policy. Personal Information collected for other travelers is only done for the purpose of providing such information to the appropriate travel supplier with the goal of fulfilling the requested service.\nWith Whom We May Share Information\n\n\nFor the purpose of conducting our business smoothly and providing seamless customer service, we frequently avail the services of third-party vendors like payment processing companies, cloud and server providing companies, business analytics providers, technological partners, marketing and distribution companies, etc. At times, we may also authorize third-party vendors to collect information on our behalf to operate certain features of our services and improve user experience. With these objectives in mind, we provide access to information to our third-party vendors to perform their functions. However, third-party vendors are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose.\n\n\nMoreover, Dudeways reserves the right to share information under the following circumstances:\n\n\n    In response to subpoenas, court orders, legal proceedings; to establish our legal rights, to defend against any legal claims, or as otherwise required by law;\n    As we find it appropriate to investigate, take action against illegal activity or suspected prohibited practices, or to uphold the right, property, and ensure the safety of our customers and the company;\n    Under unlikely scenarios of different corporate measures like divestiture, merger and acquisitions, asset sale, bankruptcy, etc.\n\n\nOther than the circumstances laid out above, you will be notified prior to sharing your personal information with any third party and you will have the option to opt-out by choosing not to share any such information.\n\n\nBesides, we sometimes share anonymous information with third parties like our advertisers and investors. The information does not contain any personal information and it is purely intended to develop our customer service quality and enhance user experience.\nVisiting From Outside the United States\n\n\nRegardless of the place of domicile of the customer, Dudeways stores the information of the customer in the United States where our central server is located and our central database is operated. As it may be the case that the privacy policy in the United States may not be as comprehensive as the one outside from where the customer is visiting, Dudeways assures you that our priority is to protect your privacy.\nLog Data\n\n\nLike many service providers, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you use our services (\"Log Data\").\n\n\nThis Log Data may include information such as your computer\'s Internet Protocol (\"IP\") address, browser type, browser version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.\n\n\nIn addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor, and analyze this data.\nDo Not Track Disclosure (\"DNT\")\n\n\nWe do not respond to DNT signals, as the definitions, common approaches, and meaning of the policy are not fully defined yet. However, you will be able to adjust your privacy preferences on your search engine, as well as your accounts you use to create a Dudeways account.\nCommunications\n\n\nWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that may be important. You will have an option to opt-out of this service. However, you may not receive emails and notifications about the changes to the Privacy Policy or Terms and Conditions. Your continued use of the service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.\nCookies\n\n\nCookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser and stored on your computer\'s hard drive.\n\n\nLike many services, we use \"cookies\" to collect information to improve our services and the user’s overall experience. Cookies are also used to follow what links you click. We or third-party websites may use this data to show you advertisements on our or other sites. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You will be able to click “help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions on how to do this. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our services or they might not work properly.\n\n\nWhen you use Dudeways, third parties may place cookies on their browsers for targeted advertising purposes.\n\n\nA list of all the types of personal data collected by Dudeways includes, for example, IP addresses, cookie identifiers, or other tracking technologies such as pixels, and end-user activity.\n\n\n\n\nWe will not retain your information any longer after you delete your Dudeways account. However, the information might take time to be completely removed from the system but it will not be used to identify or market. We may retain certain non-identifiable data for analytical purposes.\nSecurity\n\n\nThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you use links to enter third-party websites, we are not responsible for your Personal or any other information, nor are we guaranteeing that they use your personal and non-personal information the same way as we do. You should check with each individual website’s own Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before continuing to use them.\n\n\nAlso, you should keep in mind that all photographs, travel details, and comments you post, as well as your profile picture, account page, and username, can be seen and accessed by other users. These may reveal your ethnicity, nationality, location, religion, and/or sexual orientation. We are not responsible for what information you share and if there is any harm caused due to your sharing of the information.\n\n\nOnce you delete your account, it will take some time to be completely removed from the system. However, other users will not be able to see your account, although they may be able to read your public postings and comments you have made.\nThird-Party Accounts\n\n\nYou will have an option to create a Dudeways account through an email or through an already existing Facebook, LinkedIn, or Google account. Dudeways does not store your Dudeways, Facebook, LinkedIn, or Google account passwords. Your account information is not disclosed to Dudeways and you are free to cancel any of your social networking website connections with Dudeways at any time. We do not collect or gain access to your Facebook, LinkedIn, or Google pictures, locations, statuses, or any other data unless it is made public, which could include such as email addresses, profile pictures, friend lists, and birthdates. You will have an option to choose if you want to invite your Facebook friends to Dudeways and what information you share via Facebook or other networking sites. We do not control this and we are not responsible for the content in third-party accounts.\nThird-Party Websites\n\n\nOur services may contain several places where you are able to click on a link to access other websites, such as for information and advertisement. These websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy and we do not control them or what information they might collect from you. You should check each third-party website\'s own Privacy Policies and Terms and Conditions. Other users may provide links as well, but we are not responsible for the content nor do we control or check them. You should access those websites at your own risk.\nChanges To This Privacy Policy\n\n\nThis Privacy Policy is effective as of October 6, 2020, and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.\n\n\nWe reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to such changes you should not continue to use the services.\nChildren\'s Privacy\n\n\nAnyone below the age of 18 should not use the services. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under the age of 18.\nEnforcement\n\n\nWe regularly review our own compliance with our Privacy Policy. If you submit a formal written complaint with your contact information, we will try our best to resolve the issue.\nContact Us\n\n\nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or notice activity against it, please contact us:\n\n\nDudeways\n\n\nContact Information \n2nd floor, last block, Annamalai street, woraiyur,Trichy,\nTamilnadu - 620018\n\nContact Gmail: Dudeways24@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition">These Terms and Conditions (\"Terms\", \"Terms and Conditions\") govern your relationship with Dudeways (\"us\", \"we\", or \"our\"). Please read these Terms carefully before using our services. Your access to and use of our services is conditioned upon your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users, and others who access or use our services.\n\n\nBy accessing or using our services, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the Terms, then you may not access our services.\nAccounts\n\n\nWhen you create an account with us, you must provide us with information that is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a breach of the Terms, which may result in the immediate termination of your account on our service.\n\n\nYou are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access our services and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your password is with our service or a third-party service.\n\n\nYou agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.\nUser Conduct\n\n\nYou agree not to use our services for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms. You agree to abide by all applicable local, state, national, and international laws and regulations. You also agree not to:\n\n\n    Use our services in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the services or interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment of the services.\n    Obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the services.\n    Impersonate or misrepresent your affiliation with any person or entity.\n\n\nIntellectual Property\n\n\nThe service and its original content, features, and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of Dudeways and its licensors. The service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of Dudeways.\nTermination\n\n\nWe may terminate or suspend your account immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.\n\n\nUpon termination, your right to use the service will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the service.\nLimitation Of Liability\n\n\nIn no event shall Dudeways, nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from:\n\n\n    Your access to or use of or inability to access or use the service;\n    Any conduct or content of any third party on the service;\n    Any content obtained from the service; and\n    Unauthorized access, use, or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence), or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.\n\n\nDisclaimer\n\n\nYour use of the service is at your sole risk. The service is provided on an \"AS IS\" and \"AS AVAILABLE\" basis. The service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement, or course of performance.\n\n\nDudeways, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that:\n\n\n    The service will function uninterrupted, secure, or available at any particular time or location;\n    Any errors or defects will be corrected;\n    The service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or\n    The results of using the service will meet your requirements.\n\n\nGoverning Law\n\n\nThese Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Ohio, United States, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.\n\n\nOur failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have had between us regarding the service.\nChanges\n\n\nWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material, we will try to provide at least 30 days\' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.\n\n\nBy continuing to access or use our service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the service.\nContact Us\n\n\nIf you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us:\n\n\nDudeways\n\nContact Information \n 2nd floor, last block, Annamalai street, woraiyur,Trichy,\nTamilnadu - 620018\n\nContact Gmail: Dudeways24@gmail.com</string>


</resources>
